Good morning, let's
start with good results.
In the same sector, you are seeing a death, it is being
seen together, it is being seen
matching. On one side, Lawrence is being seen and on the other
side, they are seeing Glenmark Life Sciences. So,
how do you have to be careful in a single second
and I think it is
very important and will be very important going forward as well. Do
n't sleep, sir. If we look at today's stock,
Life Sciences is also showing results
and is also showing performance because this was a
stop which no one had seen. In this, along with the
numbers, sir, if you
talk about I don't have dividing degree in it, sir, then the
last dividend that was given, along with 8
% dividend deal also comes.
You can see the numbers on this top, you will see the numbers from the story also.
Cross profit margin is 55%.
Right now, today it is 33%. These are big numbers,
but the important viral
DMU, ​​where Lawrence was actually hit,
if seen there, its growth will be 100%.
Cotton Cotton and 34% growth is
of this company and the non-jeep  Yesterday's revenue is
fine, just 62% off the top plane,
they are fine, it is decreasing a little bit,
its hero which comes from Glenmark, so which is also good,
think so clearly because
honestly again the stock is very chips and
trades at a fast pace, there is
no expensive stop in the valuation, the numbers are
good and Glenmark's gain,
Sardana ji is talking
about the company, so we have said that we are
sure that we will give
this Glenmark company a middle story,
no story to anyone else, so these are very
solid state of Compass One
Standard Mark, good results,
Swaraj Engines and Usha Martin, so today the first
consistent player, sir, it dates at 15 time, it is
not a mega stock, every quarter you
will see, slowly slowly it is a
peace stock, in a way, Usha
Martin has been very alive, last
seen of you mother, so so and looking at the numbers, it
seems that we should ask some stock and at
least these numbers are happening and I
just  Stop, I already
ran away, I think, it is a shop, but the numbers
were good, sir, its cross margin is 47%,
sales are above 11%, gross profit is
above 24%, son, you have been doing
this wire business since 44,
sir, it is important to see that
if you see the revenue, two cotton
wires, brother, its margin is above 11%, its margin is also
18 cents now, which is 15%
in the last quarter, and WiFi was 14%, so these are the
three stocks, sir, which I found very good
and very good, so I told you only one, the
entire action is now weak,
understand the bad ones also because when you are saying that
one company of the same sector is very good,
one is very bad, then tell me which ones are bad, the
technology is bad, sir, but again,
what is the issue that the bad ones are drinking here,
like I told you that on the first
day, friend, you should focus on global,
what is there in global companies, that you have
already paid  If there is a stock, then where there
is a little surprise, you
find a company like Glenmark or
you find a company like Kapat or Main Sir Side,
where nothing happens, then the stock will
not fall much because it is already a cheap
stock, so like Tech Mahindra, okay Tech
Mahindra, I don't know, for how many quarters,
you have been hearing since I was in CNBC that CNG will have a
15% margin, it will do it for
15 days, then you see Aaj Tak
stuck till 11:30, so the number is weak, 24 will also
remain weak, my country is also not very special that it will be
very special going forward, it is
available on time, from where will it
fall more, how will it fall because the
time can be less in
any way, you will get
56% of D high school, you will feel that way,
I always think that going forward, our
son Mahajan will not decrease by 20%, 21%,
but in this, as I told you, if you
see, its CD is the business
where it got hit, it was thought that sales of 600 crores would
come in front of that.  ₹230 crore came in
as I said that you
saw the opposite in Glenmark Lifestyle and the way
you know Lawrence did not do it, employer sir,
revenue declined, I think second part
second is a subjective quote, I am saying again and again that
in technology you don't just have to
look at the name of the company, you have to see
which sector it is serving, the pain is that
statement from VF, in banking,
financial services, telecom, there is
more pain in them, where
Mahindra is impressed, where they do
more, there is Sun's Fox and there is
Master's Fox,
you think sir, from this in a minute,
in a technology segment, there is a complete one, it
says that I will do 30 to 40 questions of growth
and here if we go ahead and do the group of some company, then
how much difference is there and it depends on
who their clients are and
who the client is,
all this is bad and friends, this stock is currently
in the city, I think they have given a loss of ₹2m on
their investment in some years, due to that
your position is looking very bad, but because
we, this stock is never  Performed by I do
n't know, it has been so long, their numbers have
not come anywhere, just look at any segment
and most importantly, if I do
n't even see the profit, I always see Hubli,
you not talk like this things are of N group, then the
capital market segment is almost
flat, I go single digital growth, then there are
no increasing numbers from the story
and one stock sir, where I think
many people are at home is Pneumatic, I think a lot of
because the management held many meetings and
did a lot but the numbers did not come properly,
this time the sales were down by 10%, till now it was down by 40%,
now the margin which has weakened by 20% has become
13%, so this is other you know big
stroke, the numbers are as per
expectations, in line with these numbers,
Ambuja's numbers will be more important, which
I think will come on Tuesday, those numbers are
more important, at least it is seen
that there is growth in it,
this cost has to be controlled, which is a good
think, you AC has happened, in my
opinion, we do not keep buying the results,  There is more because buy back,
so buy back is already
supporting the price, how much has the buy back increased,
how has the people got more interest in the buy back, so that
is the LTMI 3 again,
sir, his comments have always been very good, his
guidance has been aggressive, his comments seem
aggressive here too because the revenue from the
point was 7%,
but I just LTD, my comments are also aggressive,
if you have faith in the country then it is a
good thing and according to me, the
numbers
in speed are better than what people had thought,
but the important thing is that
you are seeing that all these, which
we saw after the wide, that we are going for revenge,
which you keep saying, average,
good Varinder, I have a question, some innocent one
[music]
[laughs]
Shirt
to our viewers, and we will meet you on Monday, if not
Tuesday, till then there will be more
results,
thank you for discussing, so match